이 얘긴 꼭 해야겠어요
Okay, I have
to say this.
우리 다신 이런 거 하지 마요
We should never
do that again.
임무 끝났어, 척
Mission's
over, Chuck.
계획대로 잘 됐잖아
Plan went just fine.
네, 그 계획이란 게
우리가 직접 배관공사를
Yeah, except that
your plan necessitated
해야한다는 게 문제였지만요
that we do actual plumbing.
게다가 우리 중에
배관공사 할 줄 아는 사람도 없잖아요
And, for the record, none of
us knows how to actually plumb.
우리 이 옷 태울거죠?
We're going to burn
these jumpsuits, right?
나도 동의해
I second Chuck's motion.
앞으론 임무 계획에
배관공사 같은 건 넣지마
No more plumbing
on future missions.
워커, 갑자기 왜 이렇게 물러졌어?
What, are you going
soft, Walker, huh?
배관공사쯤 하면 어때
It doesn't matter.
장군님이 원하신
정보도 얻었고
Beckman got the intel
she wanted.
계집애들처럼 굴기는
Bunch of nancies. Ew.
케이시네서
옷 갈아입어야 하지 않을까요?
You need to change
at Casey's?
네? 아뇨 괜찮아요
Huh? Oh, no, thanks.
엘리랑 캡틴이
결혼식장 알아보러 갔거든요
Actually, Ellie and Awesome
are out of town
looking for a wedding site.
그래서 200번쯤 샤워할 수 있어요
So I'm good to shower
a couple hundred times.
그래요
Okay.
내일 보는 거죠?
I'll see you tomorrow?
새라, 장군님한테
오리온 얘기 들은 거 없어요?
Sarah, have you heard anything
from Beckman about Orion?
Uh, not yet.
아직은요
시간이 좀 걸릴 거예요
These things take time.
네 그렇겠죠
Gotcha. Okay.
She gets how important it is,
though, right?
그치만 이게 얼마나 중요한 일인지
장군님도 아시겠죠?
우리가 오리온을 찾아내면
I mean, you know,
if we could find Orion,
내 머릿속에서
비밀 정보들을 빼내고
then maybe I can get all
these secrets out of my head,
예전 삶으로 돌아갈 수도
있다는 거요
and go back to my old life.
당연하죠, 척
She gets it, Chuck.
우리 모두 알아요
We all do.
새라도 그걸 원하는 거 맞죠?
You want that, too, right?
당연하죠, 척
Of course I do, Chuck.
Of course.
당연히 원하죠
- 그럴 자격 있어요
- 다행이네요
I mean, you deserve that.
- Great.
정말 잘됐어요
That's-That's great.
난 장군님 사무실은
영상으로밖엔 본 적 없지만
I mean, I've only seen that
little bit of Beckman's office
behind her chair,
옆 방에 오리온을 찾고 있는
but I can only
imagine she's got
a whole crack squad
of brilliant analysts
뛰어난 분석가들이
잔뜩 있을 것만 같아요
working hard trying to find
Orion in the next room.
Chuck,
척
그니까 오리온 찾는 건
분석가들한테 맡기고
leave the search for Orion up to
the team of brilliant analysts.
이제 가서 푹 자요
You need to
get some sleep.
왜 켜졌지?
Why are you on?
홍콩
All clear.
아무도 없습니다
큰일이군
오리온이 사라졌어
Alert FULCRUM-- Orion's gone.
Ice.
얼음이야
He was just here.
방금까지 여기 있었어
Let's go.
가자 컴퓨터 챙겨
Get the computer.
한 잔 하겠나?
풀크럼이 오늘 하루 힘들었을텐데
앞으론 더 힘들어질 거야
Incoming!
Take cover!
이쪽으로 온다!
엄호해!
어서들 피해!
Down, down!
Get down!
뭐야, 언제 이렇게 된 거야?
Wh...? When did this happen?
밤에
During the night.
긍정적으로 생각해
Look on the bright side.
덕분에 몇 년은
화장지 안 사도 되잖아
We don't have to buy TP
for, like, years.
진작 해주지
Why start now?
이럴 순 없어
우리들 집을 더럽힌 거야
Oh, no.
They defiled our home here.
This is our castle.
여긴 우리의 요새라고
왜 이런 짓을 한 거지?
Why would someone do this?
대체 누구야?
Who could do this?
드디어! 누가 여길
깨끗하게 치워줬네
Finally!
Someone tried to clean up
this store.
바클레이
Barclay.
비벌리 힐스 지점
부매니저 바클레이님이시다
Assistant Manager Barclay.
Beverly Hills Branch.
Or, for you, "sir."
넌 나한테 "부매니저님" 해야지
I should have brought my resume.
이력서를 가져오는 건데
Ouch.
그래, 바클레이
So, Bar-clay,
너네가 이래놨구나?
you guys did this, huh?
우린 안 넘어가, 바토스키
Clever trick, Bartowski.
우린 아무짓도 안 했어
We admit nothing.
우리가 버뱅크에 있긴 하지만
Although, we are in Burbank.
그건 범죄가 아니잖아?
That should be a crime.
I know, I know.
그래, 바클레이
너희들이 했다고 가정했을 때
Okay, Sir Barclay,
hypothetically speaking,
어째서 너와 네 친구들이
why would someone
like yourself
and your incredibly colorful
우리 가게에 이런 짓을 했을까?
and well-coordinated team
do this to our store?
난 알지
I know why.
안녕, 마이클
Hello, Michael.
Emmett.
에멧
바클레이
Barclay.
바클레이는 우리 지점이
You see, Barclay here is upset
비벌리 힐스 지점보다
that we're getting the new
먼저 Roark 7을 받는다고
화가 나서 저러는 거야
Roark Instruments laptop
before they do.
우리가 제일 먼저
Roark 7을 받는 거예요?
We're getting the R7
gaming laptop first?
- 아직 본 사람조차 없다던데
- Bet your britches.
No one has even seen it yet.
우리가 뛰어난 지점이니까
We're the flagship store.
당연히 우리가 제일 먼저 받아야지
We should get those computers.
뛰어나긴 개뿔
Flagship of my ass.
여기서 당장 꺼져, 바클레이
Now get out of here,
Barclay.
저기 모건이
터프하다고 생각하나?
You think Morgan
over there is tough?
이 친구에 비하면
새발의 피야
Wait till you see this guy.
저 어땠어요, 마이클?
How was that, Michael?
우리 앞으로도
그 소리 내는 게 좋겠어
We got to work
on that growl.
Uh, sir,
what are we going to do?
이제 어떻게 할까요?
내가 알려줄게
I tell you what we could do.
우리도 가서
똑같이 해주는 거예요
We could assemble
a counterstrike.
줄 스프레이 두 박스하고 또..
All right,
all I need is a couple kegs
of Silly String, and maybe...
보복 같은 건 안해
No retaliations.
차분하고 침착하게
Calm and collected.
그게 바로
바이모어다운 방법이지
That's the Buy More way.
Now, clean this place up!
여기 빨리 좀 치워!
이런
Huh.
괜찮니, 컴퓨터야?
You feeling okay, computer?
네 비밀을 알고 있다
Ah. Ha, ha, ha.
그래, 알았어
누구야?
Yeah, okay.
Who's doing this?
그래, 너 똑똑하다
Your cleverness has been noted.
인터섹트란 거 알고 있어
우리 만나야겠어
Why are we meeting?
왜 만나야 하는데?
왜냐하면 내가 오리온이니까
내 말이 들려?
You can hear me?
이 컴퓨터는 안전하지 못해
네 위치로 내 껄 하나 보내겠다
What? Hello?
Hello?
안녕, 척
Hey, Chuck!
안녕, 안녕하세요 새라
Hi. Hi. Hi, Sarah.
왜 그래요?
What was it?
그게..
Um...
내가 진작 새라한테
했어야 할 얘기가 있는데요
There's something that I
should probably tell you.
뭐? 방금 뭐라고 했나?
What? What did you say?
찾았어요
I found him.
오리온을 찾았어요
I found Orion.
아니 사실
오리온이 절 찾아낸 거죠
Or, actually, he found me
10분전 쯤에 바이모어에서요
about ten minutes ago
in the Buy More.
진짜 멋있게 해킹해서
He tapped into one of
the Nerd Herd computers
너드 허드 컴퓨터로 침투해왔어요
using, I might add,
a very cool kind of hack.
척
Chuck.
그게 어떻게 가능하지?
How is that possible?
아마 제 검색 때문인 것 같아요
I-I... It probably has something
to do with my search.
Your what?
네 뭐?
척이 풀크럼과 오리온에 대한
모든 정보를 모아서
Chuck put together everything
he knew about FULCRUM and Orion,
자동 웹 검색 시스템을 만들었대요
and then he built an
automated Web search.
그게 오리온의
컴퓨터 안전망을 감지됐나봐요
I think I hit
one of his security nets.
이런식으로 일하면 안돼, 바토스키
That's not how
this works, Bartowski.
네멋대로 작전을 수행하면 안된다고
You don't conduct
your own operations.
뭐라고 하던가?
What did he say?
오리온 말이야
Orion.
제가 인터섹트란 걸
알고 있다고 했어요
Well, he knows
I'm the Intersect.
또 저한테
컴퓨터를 보내겠다고 했고요
And he's going
to send me a computer.
어디로 보낸다는 거지?
Where's the computer going?
저한테죠
To me.
아마도요
I-I think.
몰라요, 자세한 건
얘기 못했어요
I don't... We didn't really
nail down the details.
그 컴퓨터를 안전하게
지켜야 하네
I want that computer
under lock and key.
오리온의 컴퓨터는
차세대 컴퓨터라
Orion's computers are nextgen,
군사 방어 시설을 조종하고
capable of overriding
military defenses,
심지어는 컴퓨터 전산화한
무기들을 강탈할 수도 있네
even hijacking
computerized weaponry.
그게 엄한 사람 손에
들어가면 큰일이야
God help us if it falls
into the wrong hands.
Delivery for
Charles I. Bartowski.
찰스 I 바토스키 씨께
온 배달입니다
뭔데요?
What is it?
전자제품이라는데
컴퓨터겠죠?
Says electronics.
A computer?
The Roark 7.
Roark 7 이군
빼앗아 보시지, 비벌리 힐스
Take that,
Beverly Hills.
I'm Chuck.
제가 척이에요
저한테 주고 가시면 돼요
You just leave it with me.
수고하세요
Thanks.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
영어자막 : http://www.ragbear.com
싱크수정 / 한글번역
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
# Na-na na-na na-na #
# Na-na na-na
na-na #
# Na-na na-na na-na #
# Na-na na-na
na-na #
# Na-na na-na na-na #
# Na-na na-na
na-na #
Chuck 2x17
Chuck Versus the Predator
안 왔어요
아직 안 보냈나봐요
Nothing. Orion hasn't
delivered the computer yet.
오리온이 직접 가지고 올까요?
Do you think he's going
to bring it personally?
아뇨, 우선은
멀리서 지켜볼 거예요
No, he's going
to stay away for now.
네, 알았어요
그럼 기다려야겠네요
Got it. Cool.
So we wait.
왜 나한테 말 안했어요?
Why didn't you tell me?
Um...
척, 우리한테 말도 없이
오리온에 대해 검색을 하다뇨
Chuck, your search for Orion
was a rogue operation.
그게 얼마나 위험한 짓인지 알아요?
Do you know
how dangerous that is?
엄청 위험하다고요
Very.
- 근데 새라한테 말을 안했죠
- 네, 안해줬어요
And I didn't tell you.
- And you didn't tell me.
그래요, 새라 말이 맞아요
Okay, you're right.
새라 말, 틀린 것 하나 없어요
Completely and totally right.
하지만 새라
내가 예전 인생으로 돌아가고
But, Sarah, I want to get
this thing out of my head
진정한 사랑을 찾기 위해서
인터섹트를 빼내고 싶다는데
so I can go back
to my old life
and have a chance at
a real relationship.
NSA랑 CIA에서
그걸 가만히 둘 거라고 생각해요?
Do you really think the NSA
and the CIA
are going to be cool with that?
그래도 난 믿었어야죠
You should have trusted me.
야, 여긴 왜 온 거야?
Dude, what am I doing here?
- Come on.
제프 사무실에 뭐가 있어
It's in Jeff's office.
잠깐만, 싫어
제프 사무실이라고?
Wait. No, no, no.
Jeff's office?
걱정마
꼭 봐야한다니까
Don't worry.
You got to see this.
아니 못 알아들은 모양인데
제프 사무실엔 가기 싫어
No, you don't understand.
I don't want to go
그럼 내 속이.. 불편해질 것 같아
into Jeff's office. It makes
me feel... uncomfortable.
알아, 모건
하지만 감수할 만하다니까
I know. Morgan,
it's that good.
들어와
Come on in.
Oh, it's on.
오랜만이야, 모건
Long time no see, Morgan.
나 갈래
Okay, I'm leaving.
잠깐
Wait.
이거 봐
Look at this.
이게 뭔데?
What is it?
나도 처음 보는 거야
It's like nothing
I've ever seen before.
액체 냉각식에 겉은 티타늄,
OC 프로세서야
Liquid cooled, titanium housing,
over-clocked processor.
이건 예술 작품이야
Gentlemen, this
is a work of art.
It's the Roark 7.
빅 마이크한테 주기 전에
우리가 먼저 써보는 거야
We're trying it out before
we give it to Big Mike.
우리가 걸릴지도 모르니까
넌 여기 있어야 해
You're here
in case we get caught.
그래, 빅 마이크가
너한테는 심하게 안할테니까
Yeah, we figure Big Mike
won't come down too hard
on his boy.
- Thanks.
고맙다
신원을 밝혀라
빨리 덮어, 빅 마이크가
우리가 만진 거 알아차릴 거야
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
close it, close it.
Big Mike will know
that we turned it on.
아니 그냥 밝힐 수 없다고 해
No, just say you can't identify.
그럴까? / 응
Should I?
- Yeah.
밝힐 수 없다
왜? 위험한가?
응, 위험하다
Uh, yeah, you better believe it.
항공 지원을 해줄테니
타겟을 지정해라
시뮬레이션 게임인가봐
It's a simulator game.
타겟을 뭘로 하지?
Who should we target?
바이 모어
Buy More.
오리온이 에드워드 공군 기지에 있는
Orion has taken control
무인 프레데터 드론 정찰기를
조종하고 있어
of a Predator drone
based out of Edwards.
신호가 오리온이
홍콩에서 썼던 신호와 일치해
Signal matches one
he used in Hong Kong.
타겟 쪽으로 날아가고 있어
Drone was on an armed
targeting run.
- 타겟이 뭔데?
- 제발 바이모어는 아니라고 해줘요
Is there a target?
Please don't say Buy More.
오리온이 너한테
컴퓨터를 보내긴 하나보다
Orion sent you
a computer all right.
널 죽이려는 프레데터 안에
같이 넣은 모양이지
It's inside a Predator drone
targeted to kill you.
How thoughtful.
어찌나 친절한지
대체 왜 그런 짓을..
시간이 없어요
Why would he...
There's no time.
얼른 가게를 비워야 해요
We got to get everybody
out of the store.
화재 경보기를 켜야겠어
척은 여기서 드론을 지켜봐요
Fire alarm. Okay, Chuck, you
stay here and monitor the drone.
이 게임 좀 지루하다
boredom.
꼭 진짜 프레데터를
조종하는 것 같아
Feels like we're flying
an actual Predator.
난 별 3개 줄래
I give it three stars.
겨우 3개?
너 바보냐
Three stars?
You're a cretin.
얼마나 섬세하게 잘 돼있냐
그래픽도 안 끊기잖아 / 잠시만
The details are incredible.
The graphics processor must be
running on...
Hold on a second.
왜 우리 매장을 폭발시켜?
Why are we trying to blow up
our own store here?
비벌리 힐스 지점을
폭발시키는 게 낫지 않을까?
Shouldn't we be targeting a
certain Beverly Hills location?
Guys, guys, wait.
잠시만요
The drone is changing direction.
드론이 방향을 바꿨어요
어디로 가는데요?
Where's it heading?
원격 측정기에는
윌셔와 도헤니 가 사이라고 떠요
Telemetry puts it
at the corner
of Wilshire and Doheny.
바이모어 비벌리 힐즈 점이
있는 곳이야
That's the Beverly Hills
Buy More.
Why would Orion
target another store?
오리온이 거길 왜?
오리온이 아니에요
He wouldn't.
하지만 누구짓인지 알겠어요
But I know who would.
모건을 찾아봐요
Look for Morgan.
나도 갈게요
I'm on my way.
모건, 이거 들으면 바로 전화해
Morgan, call me
as soon as you get this.
Don't think, just hit
아무 생각 말고
바로 전화해줘
the callback button right now.
No sign of Morgan, Jeff or Lester.
모건도 안 보이고
제프랑 레스터도 없어
그 멍청이들이
컴퓨터 가져간 거지?
Those morons have the computer,
don't they?
누굴 먼저 죽일까
Which one dies first?
둘은 재고실로 가봐요
Look, just go-go-go check
the loading dock, and I'll look
somewhere else. Go, now!
난 다른델 찾아볼게요
서둘러요!
잠시만
Hold on a second, guys.
또 척이야
It's Chuck again.
받지마, 컴퓨터 때문일 거야
Don't answer it;
he's after my computer.
근데 두번이나 걸었어
평소엔 안 그래
Yeah, but he's called twice; he never does that.
- It could be an emergency.
급한 일일지도 몰라
급한 일인데
왜 나한테 거는진 몰라도 말이지
Why he'd call me,
I have no idea.
안돼 모건, 받지마!
No! Morgan, no.
Hey, Chuck.
응, 척
모건, 지금 어디야?
Hey, hey. Where are you?
레스터랑 제프 사무실에 있어
Uh, with Lester
in Jeff's office.
생각보다 꽤 봐줄만 해
It's actually
very nice.
모건, 내 말 잘 들어
Morgan, you have
to listen to me.
컴퓨터로 하고 있는 거
당장 멈춰야 돼
You have to stop playing
with that computer right now.
왜, 척?
Uh, why, Chuck?
일단 내 말 믿고 멈춰!
Buddy, just trust me and do it!
그래 알았어, 척
Yeah, sure, Chuck.
거의 다 도착했어
We are almost at Beverly Hills.
이제 그만 하자
다 들켰어
Time to pull the plug,
all right? Jig is up.
- 제프 얘 좀 막아
- 정말? / 응
Jeff stop him. Yes!
- Really?
척이 그만 하라잖아!
Chuck is our leader!
싫어, 넌 맨날 걔 말이라면
꿈뻑 죽더라
No, he is your leader
for some weird reason!
아! 아프잖아
Ah! You hurt me!
내놔 레스터!
Give it to me, Lester!
No, no, no!
Chuck, you stop!
You stop right there!
- Ow!
That really hurt.
한 명만 걸려라
I want just one of them!
그만 둬
No.
새라, 여기 남자화장실이에요
Sarah, you're in
the little boys' room.
Oh.
대체 이게 무슨 일인가?
What the living heck
is going on here?
그건가?
Is that it?
그거 Roark 7 이야?
Is that the Roark 7?
아뇨, 이건...
No, uh, actually,
this is...
네 맞아요
Yes it is, sir.
가까이서 보고 싶어서 그랬어요
그래도 될 것 같아서요
We wanted to
take a closer
look at it.
I figured it'd be okay.
다 제 잘못이에요
잠깐 미쳤었나봐요
It's my fault.
Crazy me.
내일 전시할 때까지
Nobody touches this computer
그 누구도 이걸 만져선 안돼
until it goes on
display tomorrow.
우릴 지켜보는 사람들이 있어
We are being watched, people!
절대 일을 그르쳐선 안돼
We can't
screw this up!
차분하고 침착하게
Calm and collected.
Hmm.
저 친구들 때문에 걱정이에요
Such ne'er-do-wells
we have here.
에멧, 자네가 오늘 밤
보초를 서주게
Emmett, I want you
to stand guard tonight.
Nobody gets close
to this laptop,
그 누구도 노트북 근처에
오면 안돼, 알았나?
got it?
알겠습니다, 마이클
Affirmative,
Michael.
비벌리 힐스 점에서
이걸 뺏으려고 할 거야
Barclay and
the Beverly Hills boys
will be
gunning for it.
나 저 컴퓨터 꼭 갖고 싶어
I want that computer back,
Jeffrey.
내 것이어야만 해
꼭 가져야겠어
It's calling
me, and I must
have it.
야근이네, 문제 없어
An after-hours job.
No problem.
이번 임무가 정해졌네요
So I guess we know
what our mission is:
바이모어를 털어라
rob the Buy More.
오늘 밤, 폐장한 뒤에
Tonight, after
the store closes.
아무도 컴퓨터가
여깄단 걸 모르니 쉽겠어
At least nobody else
knows it's here.
잘 왔네, 빈센트
Welcome, Vincent.
자네가 홍콩에서
살아남아서 다행이군
It's good to see you survived
the Hong Kong incident.
오리온을 찾았습니다
We found Orion.
그가 홍콩에서 사용했던 신호와
일치하는 신호를
Picked up a signal matching the
computer he used in Hong Kong.
캘리포니아 주 버뱅크의
한 상점에서 포착했습니다
It originated from a retail
store in Burbank, California.
바이모어였나?
Is it a Buy
More store?
네 그렇습니다
Yes, it is.
제가 그 곳으로 가볼까요?
Would you like me
to pick something up for you?
그 곳에서
풀크럼 요원 여럿을 잃었네
FULCRUM has lost
operatives there.
우린 그 곳에 CIA 지국이
있다고 생각하고 있네
We believe
it's a CIA substation.
위험 부담이 너무 커
The risk is too
great for an operation.
다들 절 잘 아시지 않습니까
Sir, madam, you know me.
그냥 두고 볼 순 없습니다
I can't let this go.
지원을 해주시지 않는다면
저 혼자라도 하겠습니다
If I don't have your support,
I'll do it myself.
그렇다면 진행하게, 빈센트
Then proceed, Vincent.
자진하여 나서줘서 고맙네
We appreciate
your initiative.
무법 지역이었지
It was a lawless town,
쉐인, 마샬 딜런,
클린트 이스트우드...
Shane, Marshal Dillon,
Clint Eastwood.
그런 카우보이들도
나에 비하면 다 꼬맹이들이지
Little girls in comparison
to Milbarge.
Rah!
Oh, God.
이번 계획은 뭐에요?
Okay, what's the plan?
너때문에 이렇게 됐는데
이번엔 네가 한번 짜봐
You got us into this mess,
why don't you
come up with the plan for once.
Okay. All right.
그래요 좋아요
그 뛰어난 스파이 기술로
에멧 주의를 돌려요
You two distract Emmett with
your super spy skills while I go
난 빅 마이크 사무실에 갈 게요
hit Big Mike's office.
마이크는 책상에
금고 비밀번호를 적어두거든요
He keeps the combination
of the safe in his desk.
비밀번호를 책상에?
Keeps the combination
in his office?
바이모어잖아요, 케이시
괜찮아요
It's a Buy More, Casey. Relax.
안돼요 안돼요
Oh, no, no, no, no.
내 계획에선 총은 못써요
There are no guns in my plan.
아무리 에멧이 짜증나게 굴어도
Okay? As annoying
as Emmett is,
쏘거나 진정제를 놓거나
가라테를 써서는 안돼요
you cannot
shoot, tranq,
or karate chop him in any way.
네가 하라고 했어
You put him in charge.
좋아
All right.
Let's go.
시작하죠
Hello?
누구 있어요?
이런, 쥐가 아니어야 할텐데
Ooh, that better not be a rat.
무슨 소리지
I'm hearing things.
프레즈노때 처럼 하면 돼
Just like Fresno.
프레즈노때 처럼
He's gonna find us.
We're gonna get fired.
들키면 바로 잘리는 거야
I'll be turning tricks again
by the end of the week.
그럼 이번 주말부터
몸을 팔아야겠지
내가 소리를 내 볼게
I can throw my voice.
그래 주의를 돌려
좋은 생각이야
A diversion, good idea.
Go, go, go.
Caw-caw.
뭐야, 무슨 소리지?
Oh, my God, what was that?
너 지금 그걸
하는 거라고 하는 거야?
Did... did you throw your voice?
그런 거 같아
I think.
이제 7시간 남았어
Seven hours to go.
거의 다 되가요, 케이시
I almost got it, Casey.
사무실로 들러왔어요
I'm in the office.
그래 잘했어 제프리
Hey, way to go, Jeffrey.
네가 소리 낸다고 한 거
퍽이나 잘하더라, 그치?
So throwing your voice really
turned out great, didn't it?
또 뭐 할 줄 아는 거 없어?
Huh? What other
tricks do you know?
여자를 자르는 마술한다고 할 땐
When you saw a
woman in half,
진짜로 자르겠다?
do you actually saw her in half?
레스터, 너 놓친 줄 알았잖아
Listen, I thought I lost you.
무서워 죽겠어
I'm scared, man.
나 오줌 싼 것 같아
I think I wet my pants.
쬐금
Just a little.
Ha.
이런 일도 생기네?
Ha. What are the chances?
두 도둑이 같은 곳을 털다니
Two burglars robbing
the same place?
참 신기한 우연도 다 있어
What a funny coincidence.
재밌군
Hilarious.
컴퓨터를 넘겨라
Give me the computer.
여기서 나가는 게 좋겠어
We got to get out of here.
레스터, 어서 가자
빨리 가자고
Lester, come on.
Let's go. Oh.
난 몇년동안이나
널 도와줬어, 제퍼슨
I've tried to help you
over the years, Jefferson.
널 최선을 다해서 도왔다고
I've drowned myself
trying to help you.
하지만 넌 멍청한 놈이야
But you're a moron.
결국 넌 그런 놈이라고
In the end, that's
what you are.
넌 바이모어 공식 멍청이야
You're a Buy Moron.
알아들어?
Do you get that?
- 알겠냐고?
- 레스터
Do you?
- Lester.
기다려봐, 제프
나 아직...
Hang on a sec, Jeff,
I just got to...
안녕하세요
Hi.
Who are you?
누구세요?
뛰어! 뛰어!
Run! Run! Run!
Run! Run!
죽어라 도둑놈들!
Die, intruders!
죽어!
Die!
엄마! 엄마!
Mother! Mother!
엄마?! 엄마!
Mother?! Mother?!
이제 알겠지
그 누구도 여길
건드릴 순 없어
That's right.
Nobody messes with
this Buy More.
절대
Nobody.
나랑 내 가게가 만만한가?
You want to mess with me
and my store?
좋아, 덤벼봐 이 놈들아
Well, bring it on, bitches!
속이 다 시원하네
That felt good.
케이시!
Casey!
- Huh?
어쩔 수 없었어
I had to that.
저기요
Guys.
기회를 주지
You get one chance.
총들을 버려라
Drop your guns.
총 가진 사람 없어요
Um, sir,
they don't have any guns.
제가 이 임무를
직접 계획했는데
I personally
put this mission together,
총은 가져오지 말라고 했거든요
and I forbade them from packing.
왜 그런 짓을 했지?
Why would you do that?
글쎄요, 제 생각엔 그냥..
I don't know.
I just, you know--
총이 있으면
일이 너무 쉬워지는 것 같아서요
I think that guns
make things too easy,
전 제 사람들이 너무
쉽게 일하는 건 원치 않았어요
and I like my spies to be tough.
아무도 안 쏘실 거죠?
Look, you're
not gonna
shoot anyone, right?
안 쏘면 프로답지 않겠지
It would be unprofessional
not to.
총을 가져왔어요?
You had a gun?!
난 총 없인 아무데도 안 가
I always have a gun.
움직이기만 해
Don't you
dare move.
저기요..
Guys...
이런 걸 보고 싶진 않았는데
I-I really didn't
need to see that.
볼로니아.. 볼로니아
Oh, sweet Bolonia.
Who's your Big Mike?
나 바빠 에멧
무슨 일이야?
I'm busy, Emmett. What?!
Okay, be
right there.
알았어, 금방 갈게
모건! 일어나!
Morgan! Wake up!
가게에 문제가 생겼대
We got trouble at the store!
비벌리 힐스에서
일을 벌였어
Beverly Hills
made their move!
하나님 감사합니다
Oh, thank God.
랭리에 연락했어
I contacted Langley.
내일 시체를 처리할
팀을 파견해주겠대
They'll send a team to dispose
of the body tomorrow.
난 도무지 이해할 수가 없어요
Guys, I don't understand.
정말 간단하고 쉬운 임무였는데
That was supposed to be
the easiest mission ever.
어떻게 풀크럼 요원이 나타날 수가 있죠?
How did a FULCRUM agent show up?
컴퓨터가
거기 있단 걸 어떻게 알았을까?
How did he know
the computer was there?
우리 말고 또 누가 알지?
Who else knows about it?
무서운 질문들이 한 두개가 아니에요
All right,
well, we got
plenty of scary questions,
now let's get some answers.
어서 답을 찾아보자고요
컴퓨터에서 손 떼게
Don't touch that computer.
Why?
왜요?
자네가 대화한 건
오리온이 아니었어
You weren't contacted by Orion.
네?
Uh, what?
잠시만요, 제가 인터섹트란 걸
알고 있었다고요
Wait, wait. He knew
that I was the Intersect.
오리온 말고
그걸 누가 알겠어요?
Who else could
possibly know that?
풀크럼
FULCRUM.
우리 분석가들은 자네가
My analysts believe
풀크럼 함정에
걸려든 거라 보고 있네
you walked into a FULCRUM trap.
Are you certain?
확실한 거예요?
전 정말..
I didn't think...
그래 생각 못 했겠지
자네들 모두 그랬을 거야
No, you didn't think.
None of you did.
자네때문에 우리의
모든 작전들이 위험해졌네
And you put this entire
operation in jeopardy.
하지만 장군님
오리온이 맞다면
But, General, if it's Orion,
이 노트북이 그와 연락할 수 있는
유일한 방법이에요
this laptop is the only way
for us to contact him.
- 소령
- 만약에 제가..
Major.
If I could just...
그런 위험을 감수할 순 없네
We can't take that risk.
NSA 기술자가
컴퓨터를 검사하게 될 거야
My NSA technicians
will inspect the computer.
Sarah, please.
새라 제발요
I'm-I'm sorry, Chuck.
미안해요, 척
어쩔 수 없어요
Orders.
장군님, 컴퓨터가 워싱턴까지 가서
General, we don't have time
검사 받는 걸 기다릴
시간이 없어요
to send this computer off
to Washington and wait.
정말 오리온이 맞다면
If this really is Orion,
다신 연락을 못할수도 있어요
he may not contact us again.
- You're right,
그래 맞아
시간이 없어
we don't have time.
그래서 이번 작전은
내가 직접 수행하겠네
That's why I'm taking over
this operation directly.
I'll be on site within the hour.
한 시간 내로 가겠네
네? 여기로 오신다고요?
What? You're coming here?
멍청한 실수 하나 때문에
바토스키 작전 전체를
Hopefully I won't have
to shut down Operation Bartowski
중단해야 하는 일이 없길 바라네
because of one foolish mistake,
하지만 풀크럼이
자네 정체를 알고 있다면
but if FULCRUM knows
who you really are,
가방을 싸서 나와 함께 가야할 거야
pack your bags, Chuck.
You're leaving with me.
자네 가족과 친구들에겐..
Tell your family and friends...
아무 말도 못하고 말이야
Tell them nothing.
장군님, 이렇게 애원할게요
General, I implore you.
애원한다곤 하지 말자
Don't use "implore."
실제로 내가 쓰는 말을 쓰자
Only use words
that you actually use.
제가 그 사람이 진정 오리온이라고
생각하는 이유는요..
Here's why I think
that Orion is legit.
나 진정이란 말도 안 쓰잖아
I don't say "legit."
- Chuck.
척 / 장군님 도착하셨어요?
Is Beckman here?
아뇨, 오고 계세요
Uh, she's on her way.
- 그럼, 컴퓨터는요?
- 요새 안에 있어
Okay. What about the computer?
- It's inside Castle.
장군님 부대가
워싱턴까지 안전하게 가져갈 거야
Beckman has a containment unit
en route to move it out.
Guys, look, I am certain that
Orion is not FULCRUM, okay?
난 오리온이
풀크럼이 아니라고 확신해요
This is the real guy.
정말 오리온이라고요
장군님이 나한테
5~45분만 시간을 주시면
If I could just get five
to 45 minutes with her,
제가 설득할 수 있어요
I could convince
the General.
아뇨, 만나고 싶지 않으시대요
No, she doesn't want
to see you.
Please just wait
in your room.
그니까 방에 가서 기다리세요
Secure the perimeter.
주변 지역 안전을 확보하라
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about my search, but...
검색 얘기 늦게 해서
미안해요, 하지만..
괜찮아요
내가 잘 말씀드릴게요
It's okay.
I'll explain it to her.
Now, go.
어서 가요
이상 없습니다
All clear.
Is the asset secure?
척은 안전한가?
Yes, ma'am.
네, 장군님
It was a highly
professional team, Michael.
정말 전문가들이었어요, 마이클
There must have been 30...
제 생각엔 한 30명..
40 of them.
40명 쯤 있던 것 같아요
They stormed the store.
가게로 난입해 오더니
And they took the new laptop.
새로 나온 그 노트북도 훔쳐갔어요
누구 같아요?
바클레이일까요?
What do you think?
Barclay?
Whoever did this broke
some serious laws here, boss.
누가 범인이든
이건 중죄에요, 매니저님
It's Barclay, all right.
분명 바클레이일 거야
I can smell him all over this.
그 녀석 냄새가 나
듣자마자 바로 달려왔어요
Hey! We came
as soon as we heard.
Heard what?
Nobody called you.
뭘 들어?
너네한텐 연락 안했는데
Mm-hmm. Correct.
네, 그렇죠 맞아요
Bingo. Yeah, no,
they closed the tap at Benny's,
걔들이 베니건스에서 술 먹고
난동을 부리길래
혹시 무슨 일 있나 싶어서 왔어요
saw the commotion,
wanted to see what was going on.
I'm calling the police.
경찰에 신고해야겠어요
Put that phone down.
Oh, God.
전화기 내려놔
We can't let them
get away with this.
그냥 넘어가선 안돼요
Okay, we can't be calm
and collected this time.
이번엔 차분하고 침착하면 안돼요
Let me see it.
손 내려봐
Mm-hmm.
No, Morgan.
아니, 모건
우린 그래도
차분하고 침착할 거야
We will remain
calm and collected.
We will be calm
and collected
오늘밤 비벌리 힐스 점에 가서도
차분하고 침착할 거고
when we go to
Beverly Hills tonight
차분하고 침착하게
and we will be
calm and collected
가게에 들어가면서
내 매니저 코드를 누를 거야
when I use my manager's
code to get into the store.
And then we will be
그리고 차분하고 침착하게
그 사랑스러운 가게를
calm and collected when we
척
잿더미로 만들어줄 거야
burn that mother loving
store to the ground.
우리가 정확하게
뭘 하러 가는 거예요?
Sir, what exactly
are we doing here?
Payback.
복수
I see.
그렇군요
그 복수에
불법적인 일도 들어가나요?
Does payback involve
illegal activities?
Damn well better.
그럼 더 좋고
척 일어나
여보세요, 척입니다
Hello, this is Chuck speaking.
Hello, Chuck.
안녕, 척
내 컴퓨터는 어디 있나?
Where's my computer?
Orion... Orion?
오리온이에요?
저기.. 컴퓨터는 지금
정부 일급 비밀 시설에 있어요
Um... uh, unfortunately,
your computer
is currently locked up in a
top secret government facility.
You have to get it.
자네가 가서 가져와
I can't.
못 해요
My handlers think
that you're FULCRUM,
제 관리자들은
당신이 풀크럼이라고 생각해요
and to be perfectly honest,
I'm on the fence myself.
솔직히 말해서
나도 확신이 안 서고요
난 풀크럼 요원이 아니야
I'm not FULCRUM.
Thanks.
고마워요
Thanks, I'm glad
we cleared that up,
그렇게 말해준 건 고마운데
but how can I be certain?
그 말을 어떻게 믿어요?
Look at your computer.
컴퓨터를 봐
How did you know
that was in the Intersect?
그게 인터섹트 정보 중
하나란 걸 어떻게 알았죠?
I put it there.
내가 넣었으니까
오래 전에
A long time ago.
You really are Orion.
당신 정말 오리온이군요
Wake up, Casey.
정신 차리게, 케이시
아직도 1980년대인줄 아나
(미국 로날드 레이건 사진)
The '80s are over.
아까는 척에게 거짓말을 했네
I lied to Chuck earlier.
척이 그 누구도
해내지 못한 일을 했어
He's done what no one else
could do.
찾아냈네
He found him.
척이 오리온을 찾아냈어
Chuck found Orion.
장군님, 왜 그러신 거예요?
General, why
lie to him?
오리온이 이 프로젝트와
척에게 얼마나 중요하다고요
Orion is extremely important
to this project and to Chuck.
Important?
중요해?
Don't think for a second
that you can tell me
뭐가 중요한지 자네가
내게 알려줄 필요는 없네, 워커 요원
what is important, Agent Walker.
I've had an army of
analysts and spies
우리 분석가들과 스파이들이
자네가 사춘기 소녀가
되기 전부터
오리온을 찾아다녔네
hunting for Orion since before
you were in a training bra.
첫 사이퍼가 완성된 후
After the first Cipher
was completed,
오리온은 자신의 개인 정보를
모두 없애고 사라졌어
Orion purged his personal
records and disappeared.
We've been looking for him
ever since.
그 이후, 우린 계속
그를 찾아다녔고
So has FULCRUM.
풀크럼도 그랬었지
Neither of us
has been able
두 기관 모두
오리온을 찾지 못했었네
to lay a hand
on him.
Until now.
지금까지
Until Bartowski.
척이 해내기 전까진
어서 가
You need to go.
No, look, I have to tell Sarah
안돼요, 방금 그걸
새라랑 케이시한테 알려줘야죠
and Casey what you just did.
당신이 오리온이란 증거잖아요
It's proof that you're Orion.
게다가 안마당에
요원들이 지키고 서있고
And, on another note,
I've got a small convention
of agents gathered
in my courtyard, and my team
is in a high-level meeting.
우리 팀원들은
중요한 미팅중이란 말예요
그들을 믿어선 안 돼
You can't trust them.
사라랑 케이시요?
Who, Sarah and Casey?
매일 매일 내 목숨을
구해주는 사람들이에요
They save my life
on a regular basis.
컴퓨터 앞으로 가봐
Go to your computer.
우리가 정말 오리온을
상대하고 있는 거군요
So, we're dealing
with the real Orion.
얼마나 위험한 자죠?
How dangerous is he?
홍콩에서 풀크럼이 접근해오자
When FULCRUM made a
move on him in Hong Kong,
훔친 프레데터로
빌딩 대부분을 폭발시켰네
he nearly destroyed
an entire building
with a stolen
Predator.
Wow.
Beckman is tiny.
장군님 되게 작네
장군님, 만약에 오리온이
척 머릿속에서
General, what if Orion
can help Chuck
인터섹트를 제거하고
지울 수 있다면요?
remove the Intersect,
erase it from his mind?
Yeah, yeah.
잘했어요
좋은 질문이에요, 새라
Good question, Sarah.
난 제거하지 않길 원하네
That's exactly
what I don't want.
척 바토스키는
국가 안보에 매우 중요한 인물이야
Chuck Bartowski
is absolutely vital
to national security.
He can never
meet Orion.
절대로 오리온과
만나서는 안되네
내 말 알아들었나, 워커 요원?
Do you understand that,
Agent Walker?
Uh... yes.
네
What?
새라, 안돼요
Sarah, no.
Yes, I understand.
네, 알겠습니다
You have 40 seconds to exit.
40초내로 빠져나가야해
감시가 허술할 거야
Their surveillance is down.
What about the agents?
요원들은 어떡하고요?
Leave the watch.
시계는 두고 어서 출발해
Go now.
신원을 밝혀라
움직이지 말 것
What's happening?
이게 뭐에요?
움직이지 마
신원 확인 완료
척 바토스키
맞췄어요
그럼 누군줄 알았어요?
Uh... that's good.
Who did you think I was?
I'm sorry, I had to make certain
미안하네, 함정이
아니란 걸 확실히 해야했네
this wasn't a trap.
Orion.
오리온
Hello, Chuck.
안녕, 척
It's good to finally see you
face-to-face.
드디어 이렇게
직접 만나게 되어 반갑네
Yeah.
네, 저도요
Yeah, same here.
Can I... can I ask you
a question?
뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼요?
그럼
Of course.
The Intersect
that's in my head right now...
지금 제 머릿속에 있는
인터섹트요..
You want to get it out,
don't you?
지우고 싶다고?
네, 꼭 지우고 싶어요
Yes, yes, I very much do.
우선 만나야겠네
We need to meet first.
네, 좋아요
Okay, yeah, yeah.
언제든 말씀만 하세요
My calendar is pretty wide open.
When can we meet tonight?
오늘밤 언제가 좋은가?
Tonight?
오늘밤이요?
지금 LA에 있네
I'm in Los Angeles.
할 얘기가 많겠군
여기로 오게
We have much to discuss--
meet me here
in an hour.
1시간 후에
Orion out.
오리온 나감
Okay.
알았어요
Chuck out.
척도 나감
소리 지르지마
Don't scream.
안 그래도 머리 아파 죽겠으니까
I have a splitting
headache.
Oh, oh, oh.
You're... you're
not dead.
안 죽었네
'테트로도톡신' 이라는 거다
A modified poison
복어에서 추출한 독을
변형한 독이지
extracted from blowfish.
FULCRUM agents are taught
to survive its near-death state.
풀크럼 요원들은 이 방법으로
죽었다 살아나는 법을 배워
참 재밌는 수업이겠다
That sounds like a fun class.
Not really.
아니 별로
Now...
자, 지금부터
내가 시키는대로 해
I need you to do
exactly as I say.
Stand up.
일어서
일어..나라고
Stand up... I'm standing.
Oh, oh, oh!
미안
Sorry, sorry.
Let's go.
가지
바토스키가 뭘 원하던
난 관심 없네
I don't care what
Bartowski thinks he wants.
I want Orion.
- General.
- 난 오리온을 원해
- 장군님
뭔가, 워커?
What is it, Walker?
꼭 드리고 싶은 말씀이 있어요
I need to say something.
척 바토스키는 조국을 위해
목숨을 걸고 일하고 있어요
Chuck Bartowski has
risked his life
for this country.
하지만 스파이는 아니란 걸
자기 자신도 잘 알고 있고요
But he's not a spy,
and he knows it.
내가 아니라고 할 때까진
스파이야
He's a spy until I say he isn't.
장군님, 오리온이
있다는 걸 척이 뻔히 아는데
General, Chuck knows
that Orion is out there,
그냥 방에 앉아서 우리가
시키는대로 할리가 없어요
and he is not going to just sit
in his room and do what we say.
분명..
He...
- 왜 그래?
- 척 어딨어?
What is it?
Where is Chuck?
The watch has
him in his room.
시계를 봐선 방에 있는데
아냐, 우리가 아는
척은 이럴리가 없어
No, this is Chuck
we're talking about.
무슨 변명거리를 만들어서
여길 나타나서
He would have come up
with some excuse to come in here
- 장군님을 직접 만나려고 했어야해
- 뭐라고?
and meet the general in person.
- What?
- 방을 확인해봐
- 워커 요원 말이 맞습니다
Check his room.
- Walker's right.
Chuck's a social butterfly
by nature.
척이 워낙 사회성이 좋아서
Checking the Castle.
요새를 확인해볼게요
아냐 잠시만 기다려봐
테잎을 뒤로 돌려보자
No, wait, wait, wait,
run the tape back.
뭔가 더 있을 거야
There's got
to be something else.
척이 뭔가 힌트를 남겨뒀을 거야
좋아
Okay.
I shut off the security cameras.
보안 카메라를 껐어
안 보일 거야
We're clear.
세상에
My God.
너무 아름다워요
It's beautiful.
정말 깨끗하고..
Oh, it's so clean
산뜻한 게 꼭....
and fresh, like...
- 질 세척기
- 맙소사
Douches.
Oh, my God.
Oh, hey.
마이크, 뭐 할까요?
You know what we'll do?
- 얼굴에 장난치는 건 어때요?
- 싫어
We'll draw little
funny faces on them.
How about that?
- Nope.
- 그게 뭐에요?
- 내 바이올린
What's that?
- My fiddle.
음악 연주라도 하시려고요?
We're going to play music?
- 응
- 안돼요, 잠시만요
Oh, yeah.
- No, no, hold on a second.
잠시만요
여기 기다리고 있어
Wait, wait, wait...
uh, stand by here, everybody.
잠깐 저랑 얘기 좀 하실래요?
Can I have a moment
of your time?
지금 이게 무슨 일인지
얘기 좀 해요
If we could
just, uh,
talk about
what's about to happen here,
자, 지금 기분이 어떠신지
저한테 말씀해보세요
okay, and see what emotions
start bubbling up,
and... talk.
매니저님이랑 저랑 얘기해요
You and I
will talk.
둘이서 얘기해보자고요
We'll just
talk it out.
이건 매니저님 답지 않아요
This isn't you, sir.
They hit one
of my men.
그 놈들이 내 직원을 때렸어
Then, let Emmett
have the bat, all right?
그럼 에멧이 방망이를 들게 해요
에멧이 직접
복수하게 하자고요
Let him take his revenge
out on the store.
얘 말이 대충 맞는 거 같아요
That... that sounds
vaguely sane.
주세요
Here.
저도 잘할 수 있어요
I can be destructive.
Oh.
좋아요, 그럼..
All right! So...
뭘 먼저 때려볼까요?
What to hit first?
Ah!
이건 어때요?
How about that?
알았어요, 한번 더
All right, one
more time.
감정을 실어서
With feeling.
Oh, God.
오 이런
자, 얘들아..
Okay, team...
얼른 도망쳐
We should run now.
바이모어 만세!
Viva la Buy More!
Burbank style!
오리온을 안지 얼마나 됐지?
How long have you
known Orion?
안다고 할 수 있는 사이는 아니야
I don't really know him.
You're CIA, right?
너 CIA 요원이지?
Sure.
그래
Name's Carmichael.
이름은 카마이클
들어본 적 있어
I've heard of you.
Orion was coming out
of the cold for you.
너 때문에 오리온이
밖으로 나오다니
실력이 대단하군
That's excellent work.
I've been after him
for three years.
난 3년째
오리온을 쫓고 있어
네 비밀이 뭐지?
What's your secret?
동쪽에서 누가 옵니다
Someone's
approaching from the east.
I need you to stand
by the window
오리온이 널 볼 수 있게
창문 옆에 서 있어
so Orion can see you.
안전한가?
Tell him it's safe.
안전하다고 해
안전하다고 하라고
Tell him it's safe.
안전해요
Yeah, it's safe.
아랫층으로 와
Take him!
잡아
도망쳐
도망쳐 척
지붕으로 데려가
헬리콥터가 오고 있으니까
Take him to the roof.
Chopper's on the way.
On behalf of FULCRUM,
내가 풀크럼을 대신해서
고맙단 인사를 해야겠군
카마이클 요원
I'd like to thank you,
Agent Carmichael.
자네에게 적절한 보상을
해주고 싶지만
I wish I could give
you a proper reward.
아쉽게도 널 쏠 수밖에 없군
But, fortunately,
I have to shoot you.
안 쏘는 건 프로답지 않을테니까
It would be
unprofessional not to.
Chopper is here.
Move out now. Now!
오리온을 데려갔어요!
No, no, they have Orion!
지붕 위로 데려간다고 했어요
They're gonna take him
to the roof!
- 안돼요, 우린..
- 내가 구할 거예요!
No, we're not...
- I can save him!
척!
Chuck!
안돼!
No!
What does that mean?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
모르겠어요
I don't know.
Yes, General, I read you.
네 장군님 알겠습니다
여기서 빨리 빠져 나가야해
We have to get
outta here.
프레데터가 이쪽으로 오고 있대
A Predator's heading toward us.
헬기를 폭발시키려는 거예요
He's trying to take himself out.
척, 어서 가요
Chuck, we have to go now.
안 가요, 내가 할 수 있어요
No, no, I can do this.
프레데터를 다시
프로그램하면 돼요
I can reprogram the Predator.
제발!
Come on!
빨리 가자, 척
We are leaving, Chuck.
싫어요 안 가요
내가 구할 거예요
No! No, no, no,
I have to do this.
죽으면 안돼요!
He can't die!
척, 구할 수 없어요
Chuck,
you can't save him.
이번엔 척이
할 수 있는 일이 없어요
Okay, you can't fix this one.
오리온이 풀크럼에게
잡혀가는 것보단 낫네
It's better that Orion didn't
fall into FULCRUM's hands.
그들이 자신한테
어떻게 할지 알고
He knew what they
would do to him.
정보를 얻지 못하기 위해 그런 거야
He knew what they would gain.
장군님은 제 머릿속에서
인터섹트를 지우는 게 싫으시죠?
General, you don't
want the Intersect
out of my head, do you?
No, I don't.
그래, 싫네
Ma'am, Chuck has done everything
that we've asked of him.
장군님, 척은 항상 저희가
하자는대로 따라줬습니다
워커 요원
척을 보호하고 싶은 건 알겠네
Agent Walker,
you want to protect him.
하지만 놀이는 끝났어
But playtime is over.
척, 이런 말을 해도 될지 모르겠지만
Chuck, I hesitate to say this.
네, 그럼 하지 마세요
Please, please, hesitate.
We are in the midst
of a secret war with FULCRUM.
우린 지금 풀크럼과
은밀한 전쟁을 치루고 있네
그리고 난 이 전쟁의 결과는
And I believe the
outcome of this fight
전적으로 자네에게
달려있다고 생각하네
will rest squarely
on your shoulders.
Oy.
아뇨, 케이시가 맞아요
No, listen to the man.
He's right.
옳은 말이에요
전 스파이가 아니에요
I'm no spy.
내가 풀크럼 때문에
얼마나 많은 요원들을 잃었는지 아나?
Do you know how many agents
I've lost to FULCRUM?
얼마나 뛰어난 요원이었는지 알아?
How powerful they are?
많은 작전 중에 이 작전에서만
Only this operation,
바로 자네만이
풀크럼의 구멍을 찾아냈어
only you have found
a hole in their armor.
See, I can't lose you, Chuck.
알겠나? 난 자넬 놓칠 수 없네
I need you.
자네가 필요해
이제 자네가 스파이가 되어야해
It's time for you
to become a spy.
Yes!
- Yes!
아침 버뱅크의 냄새가 너무 좋아
Love the smell of Burbank
in the morning!
이 승리의 냄새!
Smells like victory!
이봐
Hey!
무슨 짓을 했는지 다 알아
We know what you did.
이제 알았어?
Well, do you now?
너무 멀리갔어, 마이클
You went too
far, Michael.
경찰에 신고하겠어
I'm calling the cops.
아니, 안할 거잖아
No, you won't.
It ain't the Buy More way.
그건 바이모어 답지 않으니까
뭐?
What?
규칙을 알잖아
You know the rules.
다른 마트에서
가격을 10% 내리면
They cut their prices by 10%,
우린 15%를 내려
we cut ours 15.
토스트기를 증정품으로 주면
우린 전자레인지를 주지
They give away toasters,
we give away microwaves.
우리 직원을 건드리면
They put their hands
on one of ours,
우린 그 마트
부매니저를 찾아가서..
we find their
assistant manager and...
무슨 소린지 알겠지?
You get the picture, don't you?
이만 가자
We're leaving.
하지만 내 가게와
But speaking for my store
비벌리 힐즈 전체를
대신해서 말하는데
and the city of
Beverly Hills as a whole,
우린 너희들 방법을
인정할 수 없어
we do not approve
of your methods.
그거야 네가 버뱅크 출신이 아니니까
Well, you're not
from Burbank.
Hah!
그 때 날 막아줘서 고마워
Thanks for stopping me
back there.
우리 매장에
더 이상의 문제는 필요없잖아
The store doesn't need any more
trouble than it's already got.
What is it, sir?
매장에 문제있어요?
소문이 있어
Rumors mostly.
이 지역 매장을
폐쇄할 수도 있다고 하더라고
There's been some talk about
a store in the area closing.
사람들이 해고당하고..
요즘 경기가 안 좋잖나
People being fired--
Times are tough.
네, 그렇죠
Sure, yeah.
그걸 두고 볼 순 없죠
We can't let that happen.
걱정마
Don't worry, son.
두고보지 않을 거야
We won't.
척, 자네가 이걸 보게 된다면
내게 무슨 일이 생겼다는 뜻이겠군
If you're watching this, Chuck,
it means something
happened to me.
Probably something not so nice.
아마 썩 좋은 일은 아니겠지
우리가 직접 만나서
Well, I hope we were able
to meet,
자네에게 내 본명을
말해주고 싶었어
I hope I was able
to tell you my real name.
자네에게 준 카드들은
새 인터섹트의 개략도야
The cards you're looking at
are the schematics
for the new Intersect.
풀크럼에서 훔쳐왔지
I stole them from FULCRUM.
누구에게도 보여주지 말고
연구해봐
Show them to no one,
but study them.
자네가 인터섹트를
머릿속에서 지우고 싶다면
You will need to
understand that computer
그 컴퓨터를 제대로
이해해야하네
if you want to get the
Intersect out of your head.
And yes, it's possible.
그리고, 맞아 가능해
만약에 자네가
풀크럼의 인터섹트를 찾아내고
If you can find
FULCRUM's Intersect,
안에 담긴 정보를 얻어낸다면
if you can get inside,
예전의 삶으로
돌아갈 수 있을 거야
you could get
your old life back.
Good-bye, Chuck.
잘 있게, 척
이 디스크는 5초 후에
자동으로 소멸될 거야
This disk will self destruct
in five seconds.
Always wanted to say that.
나도 한번쯤 이렇게 말해보고 싶었어
Chuck? Hi.
She's wrong, you know.
장군님 말씀 틀린 거 알죠
I'm not a spy.
난 스파이가 아니에요
그 분은 군인이시라
Look, Beckman is a soldier
모든 걸 흑백으로만 보세요
and she see things
in black and white.
But she is right
about one thing.
하지만 한가지에 대해선
옳으셨어요
We're in the middle
of a fight with FULCRUM.
우린 지금 풀크럼과
전쟁을 치르고 있어요
Yeah, uh...
네 저도 알아요
I get that, I do.
하지만 이건 미래가 아니라
But this is not my future.
지금 나에게 벌어지고 있는
현재의 일이에요
This is what I'm
doing right now.
하지만 꼭 예전의 삶으로 돌아갈 거예요
But I will get my life back.
그럼요 당연하죠, 척
Yeah, of course you will, Chuck.
아직 우리 좋은 팀인거죠?
We're still a good team, right?
여전히 우릴 믿는 거 맞죠?
You still trust us?
새라를 믿어요
I trust you.
당연히 믿죠
Of course I do.
난 당신 편이에요, 척
I'm on your side, Chuck.
알아요
I know.
난 이만 가는 게 좋겠어요
Well, I-I better go.
Yeah.
네
네, 좀 피곤하네요
Yeah, I'm, uh,
I'm a little beat.
갈게요
Okay.
워커 요원이 임무를
잘 수행하고 있나?
Is Walker on board
with this mission, Major Casey?
Yes, ma'am, 100%.
네, 잘 하고 있습니다
워커 요원이 척을
이성으로 생각하는 건 아니고?
You have no reservations
about how she feels toward
the asset?
- No, ma'am.
아닙니다 장군님
워커와 바토스키에 대한
모든 걸 알아야겠네
I want everything you have
on her and Bartowski.
Video surveillance
보안 비디오와
솔직하게 보고서를 써서 제출하게
and your unedited report.
절 못 믿으시는 겁니까?
Don't you trust me?
난 누구도 믿지 않아
I don't trust anybody.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
Subtitles by LeapinLar